You know what I'm really disinterested in?
The not all Jews commentary right now.
We got all these files with all this supremacy in it.
And folks are finding and taking up space saying,
you guys, not all Jews think this way.
Not all Jews are Zios.
Not all Jews believe people who aren't Jewish should be harmed.
Duh!
Captain Obvious, we know that.
What has been peddled by far too many Jewish people, however,
is the idea that acknowledging a consolidation of power
by folks who all identify by the same identity
is somehow anti-Semitic.
It is not.
Anytime power is consolidated by a singular group,
it needs to be acknowledged and it needs to be challenged
and it needs to be checked
and it needs to be investigated.
And saying that, well, if you're doing that with Jewish people,
you are mimicking the attacks that the H guy said.
No, it's not mimicking because it's not done in the same interest
and it's not done with the same outcome
and it's not done from a position of power.
Not all Jews.
Guess what?
Not all white people are racist.
It doesn't matter.
Not all men are grapists.
When you're in a position of power,
it doesn't matter if not all of you are like that
because ultimately, whether you are doing the things or not,
you're still benefiting.
And unless you are outwardly, emphatically, loudly challenging them,
you are representing them.
Them people took an ethnicity and religious group
and turned it into a power source of supremacy
that has oppressed people worldwide.
Saying not all of us do that doesn't change that.
And that is where all energy needs to be put.
And I know that that is discomforting for some of you.
Some of you are going to even try and say that's anti-Semitic
because, well, that's the fashionable thing to say.
Stay focused on identifying the oppressor
and no one will confuse you with being one of them.
You're damn rude, eh?
You're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude, you're damn rude.